Guide to the Stanford University, Vice President for Business Affairs, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Vice President for Business Affairs, records
1887-1978
1913-1978
SC0677
Stanford University. Office of the Vice President for Business and Finance
Stanford University. Office of Vice President for Business Affairs.
175.5 Linear feet 117 boxes
The collection includes minutes, reports, correspondence, leases, proposals, and other records pertaining to financial and business aspects of the administration of Stanford University. Among the subjects covered by the records are property matters, land development, building projects on campus, academic departments and professional schools, faculty and student housing, the hospital and medical center, SLAC, shopping center, industrial park, Jasper Ridge, relations with Palo Alto, roads, and water. Of particular historical interest are the files on Jane and Leland Stanford's carriages, the Japanese Students Association, the isolation hospital, and Vina Ranch (which include maps).
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
The records were received by the Stanford University Archives via administrative transfer in 1997.
Information about Access
The materials are partially restricted. Gift records in boxes 5, 15, 72, and 73 are restricted for 75 years.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
The Business Affairs organization at Stanford provides integrated financial, technological, business and human resource services for the benefit of the university community.
Description of the Collection
The collection includes minutes, reports, correspondence, leases, proposals, and other records pertaining to financial and business aspects of the administration of Stanford University. Among the subjects covered by the records are property matters, land development, building projects on campus, academic departments and professional schools, faculty and student housing, the hospital and medical center, SLAC, shopping center, industrial park, Jasper Ridge, relations with Palo Alto, roads, and water. Of particular historical interest are the files on Jane and Leland Stanford's carriages, the Japanese Students Association, the isolation hospital, and Vina Ranch (which include maps).
Access Terms
Japanese Students Association (Stanford, Calif.); Stanford University -- General subdivision--Buildings.;; Stanford University. Office of Vice President for Business Affairs.; Vina Ranch (Calif.); Strategic planning -- Business; Universities and colleges--Business management; Vina Ranch (Calif.)
Collection Contents
- Abramovitz, Moses, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Abrams Estate - Letitia P. Abrams - D. B. Adams, Executor, 1964-1966 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Abrams, Herbert L., 1965-1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Abrams, Letitia P., 1937-1965 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Achievement Tests, #1, 1949-1969 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Administration Bldg. Physical Ed and Athletics Remodeling, 1974 (Box 109, Folder 14)
- Admissions Office, 1956-1972 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Affirmative Action - Plans of Outside Agencies and Communities, 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Affirmative Action Program - External, 1969-1973 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Affirmative Action Program - Internal, #1, 1969-1971 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Affirmative Action Program - Personnel, Resumes, 1963-1970 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Agreement with Urban Coalition (Frenchman’s Terrace),1970-1975 (Box 95, Folder 11)
- Agreements - Miscellaneous, 1960-1965 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Airplanes, 1958-1972 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Alameda County - Morrison Property - City of Fremont, CA, SOLD, 1955-1963 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Alameda County Property -Ellery Estate - 2124 Coloma Street, Oakland, SOLD, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Alameda County Property, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Alchohol, Tax Free Permit, 1940-1966 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Algard, F. Thomas, Jr., 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Allen, J. Garrott, 1959-1964 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Almack, Evelyn (Mrs. John C.), 1939-1968 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Alpha Delta Phi, 1949-1964 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Alpha Kappa Lambda, Inc., 1951- (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Alpha Phi Omega, 1951-1953 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Alpha Sigma Phi (Tau of) Corp., 1961-1965 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Alpha Tau Omega Bldg. Assn., 1953-1968 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Alpine House Requisitions - Payroll and other, 1959-1966 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Alternatives for Building Now or Later, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Alumni Association, 1944-1961 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Alvarado - 514 (Hawthorne House - Psyc. Dept.), 1953-1963 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Alvarado - 532 (Bolivar) - University Owned, 1957-1961 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Alvarado - 544 - University Owned, 1964-1967 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Alvarado Row - 528 - University Owned, 1953-1963 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Alvarado Row, 526 - University-owned, 1956-1964 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Alvarado Row, 556 - University-owned, 1964-1968 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Alvarado, 520, 1951-1964 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Alvarado, 536, 1948-1963 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Alvarado, 548 - University-owned, 1941-1965 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Alvarado, 552 - University-owned, 1936-1964 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Alvarado, 560 - University-owned - Branner House, 1924-1958 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Alvarado, 582 - University-owned, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- AMA R&D Commission Budget, 1977 (Box 99, Folder 21)
- American Association of University Professors, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- American Bldg. Maintenance Co. - Agreements and Understandings, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- American Bldg. Maintenance Co. - Equipment Inventory, 1960-1963 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- American Bldg. Maintenance Co., Folder III, 1964-1968 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- American Bldg. Maintenance Co., Folder IV, 1969-1971 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- American Breeders Service, 1954-1960 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- American Building Maintenance Company, #5, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- American Laundry Brochures (Box 33, Folder 53)
- Amherst Encroachment - Exhibits, 1888-1967 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Amherst Encroachment - Lot Owners, Lot 33 - Correspondence, 1950-1967 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Amherst Street Residents - Use of Lot 33, 1948-1968 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Ampex Corporation - 80 acres, 1959-1962 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Ampex Corporation - Lease, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Ampex Corporation, 1955-1962 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Anderson, Rebecca, 1946-1957 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Animal Research Center - Legal, 1967-1970 (Box 102, Folder 19)
- Ann Mason Review (W.Massy Personal File), 1977 (Box 99, Folder 18)
- Annexation - FrenchmanÕs Terrace, 1972-1975 (Box 95, Folder 12)
- Annexations - Exhibits, 1953-1961 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Applied Physics Laboratory - Bid Packages, Summaries, 626 1974 (Box 105, Folder 26)
- Applied Physics Laboratory - Budget & Fiscal, 626, 1974-1977 (Box 105, Folder 28)
- Applied Physics Laboratory - Bulletins & Supplements, 626, 1975-1976 (Box 105, Folder 30)
- Applied Physics Laboratory - Contract Changes, 626, 1975-1976 (Box 105, Folder 29)
- Applied Physics Laboratory - Disbursements, 626, File I, 1971-1977 (Box 105, Folder 27)
- Applied Physics Laboratory - Exhibits, 626, 1975 (Box 105, Folder 37)
- Applied Physics Laboratory - Field Inspectors Progress Reports, 626, 1975 (Box 105, Folder 35)
- Applied Physics Laboratory - Field Meetings, 626, 1975 (Box 105, Folder 23)
- Applied Physics Laboratory - Field Orders, 626, 1975 (Box 105, Folder 24)
- Applied Physics Laboratory - General Correspondence #1, 626, 1971-1977 (Box 105, Folder 32)
- Applied Physics Laboratory - Legal, File I, 626, 1971-1977 (Box 105, Folder 34)
- Applied Physics Laboratory - Program, 626, 1962-1974 (Box 105, Folder 25)
- Applied Physics Laboratory - Punch List, 626, 1975-1976 (Box 105, Folder 31)
- Applied Physics Laboratory - Testing Reports, 626, 1975 (Box 105, Folder 36)
- Applied Physics Laboratory - Transmittal Letters, 626, 1975 (Box 105, Folder 33)
- Applied Technology, Inc., see: Itek Corporation (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Appointment Books, 1972-1975 (Box 93)
- Appraisal - Medical Unit Bldgs. S. F., 1926-1942 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Appraisals - Industrial area - Lot 41, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Appraisals - Land Adjacent to Stanford Land, 1956-1968 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Appraisals - Merged Endowment Fund Real Estate (On Campus and Off Campus, 1946-1965 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Appraisals - Proposed (Land Development), 1945, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Architects - Land Development, 1952-1959 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Architects - Landscape - Land Development, 1948-1957 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Arnold Development Co. - Correspondence, 1956-1962 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Arnold Development Co. - Offsite Improvements - Access Road - Sondgroth Bros., 1959-1963 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Arnold Development Co. - Preliminary Proposals, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Art Building - Legal, 1964-1969 (Box 102, Folder 7)
- Asociated Students of Stanford Univ. Constitution & By-Laws (superseded) (Binder) (Box 17)
- Asociated Students of Stanford Univ. - Travel Service, #5, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Asociated Students of Stanford Univ. - Travel Service, #6, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Associated Oil Co. - Correspondence, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Associated Students of S. U. - Travel Service, 1962-1965 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Associated Students of Stanford University - Stanford Sailing Association #1, 1966-1972 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Associated Students of Stanford University - Travel Service, Folder 2, 1966-1968 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Associated Students of Stanford University - Travel Service, Folder 3, 1969-1971 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Associated Students of Stanford University - Travel Service, Folder 4, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Associated Students of Stanford University, 1, 1944-1963 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Associated Students of Stanford University, 2, 1963-1966 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Associated Students of Stanford University, 3, 1966-1968 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Associated Students of Stanford University, 4, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Associates for Radio Astronomy, 1966-1970 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Association of Independent California Colleges & Universities, Folder 2, 1965-1968 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Association of Independent California Colleges and Universities, Folder 3, 1968-1971 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Association of Independent Colleges & Universities, Folder 1, 1957-1965 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Athletics Development, Stage II - Affirmative Action Program (528), 1972-1973 (Box 115, Folder 1)
- Athletics Development, Stage II - Affirmative Action Reports, (528), 1972-1973 (Box 115, Folder 2)
- Athletics Development, Stage II, (528) - Budget & Fiscal, 1969-1974 (Box 114, Folder 16)
- Athletics Development, Stage II, (528) - Bulletins, Supplements, 1972-1973 (Box 114, Folder 19)
- Athletics Development, Stage II, (528) - Contract Changes, 1972-1974 (Box 114, Folder 18)
- Athletics Development, Stage II, (528) - Correspondence, File 1, 1968-1974 (Box 114, Folder 17)
- Athletics Development, Stage II, (528) - Correspondence, File 2, 1972-1974 (Box 114, Folder 21)
- Athletics Development, Stage II, (528) - Correspondence, File 3, 1974 (Box 114, Folder 20)
- Athletics Development, Stage II, (528) - Disbursements, File 1, 1969-1973 (Box 114, Folder 12)
- Athletics Development, Stage II, (528) - Disbursements, File 2, 1973-1974 (Box 114, Folder 11)
- Athletics Development, Stage II, (528) - Exhibits (Box 114, Folder 25)
- Athletics Development, Stage II, (528) - Field Inspector’s Progress Report, File II, 1973 (Box 114, Folder 22)
- Athletics Development, Stage II, (528) - Job Site Meetings, 1972-1973 (Box 114, Folder 15)
- Athletics Development, Stage II, (528) - Legal, File 1, 1969-1973 (Box 114, Folder 13)
- Athletics Development, Stage II, (528) - Legal, File 2, 1973 (Box 114, Folder 14)
- Athletics Development, Stage II, (528) - Testing Laboratory Reports, 1970-1973 (Box 114, Folder 24)
- Athletics Development, Stage II, (528) -Field Inspector’s Progress Reports, 1972-1973 (Box 114, Folder 23)
- Automobiles & Automotive Equipment, 3, 1962-1964 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Automobiles & Automotive Equipment, 4, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Back-Up, 1970-1971 (Box 115, Folder 22)
- Bailey Property - Mountain View (Gift of Bertha Coville Bailey), 1953 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Balch, Richard L., 1962-1964 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Baldwin, John W., 1959-1961 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Bank of California - Temporary Lease on El Camino Real (terminated) - Correspondence, 1967-1971 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- BAP II, 1970-1971 (Box 73, Folder 23)
- Bard, L. L. et al, 1946-1948 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Barkan, Hans, 1951-1955 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Bartky, Adolph J. & Ruth, 1946-1958 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Bassett, L. E., 1949-1955 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Baumberger, J. P. & A. L., 1952-1955 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Bay Area Rapid Transit District, 1961-1968 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Bay Area Water Users Association, 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Bechtel “I” Center Remodeling, 862, 1974 (Box 103, Folder 37)
- Bell, Pearl B., Estate of, 1967-1971 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- Berger, Joseph, 1963-1966 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Bergstrom, Prof. Francis William, 1939-1947 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Berkeley Big 10 + 2 Nov. 26-27, 1973 (Box 99, Folder 22)
- Berman, Samuel M., 1964-1967 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Beta Theta Pi, 1953-1965 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Bidding, 1956-1957 (Box 113, Folder 13)
- Biological Sciences 132A/42A - Relocate A.C. Unit, 660, 1970-1971 (Box 109, Folder 26)
- Biological Sciences Room 99 - Air Conditioning Study and Revisions, 659, 1971-1973 (Box 109, Folder 27)
- Biology Building - Legal Documents, 163, 1961-1967 (Box 102, Folder 13)
- Black Mountain Ranch, 1978 (Box 92, Folder 5)
- Blackwelder, Eliot, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Bldg/Remod Costs by Bldg, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Blindcraft, 1946-1954 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Blue Chip Stamp Company - Comm/L, 1956-1960 Terminated (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Blume, John A. & Associates, Engineers - Agreement to enter Conley lease, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Board of Trustees - Ad Hoc Budget Committee, October 26, 1977 (Binder) (Box 98)
- Board of Trustees - Agenda, November 8, 1977 (Binder) (Box 98)
- Board of Trustees actions - Frenchman’s Terrace, 1969-1974 (Box 95, Folder 15)
- Board of Trustees Agenda, December 13, 1977 (Binder) (Box 98)
- Board of Trustees Agenda, June 10, 1977 (Binder) (Box 98)
- Board of Trustees, April 11, 1978 (Binder) (Box 98)
- Board of Trustees, February 14, 1978 (Binder) (Box 98)
- Board of Trustees, June 16, 1978 (Binder) (Box 98)
- Board of Trustees, June 16, 1978 (Binder) (Box 98)
- Board of Trustees, May 8, 1978 (Binder) (Box 98)
- Boeninger, H. R. & H. R., 1949-1971 (Box 73, Folder 25)
- Bookstore Cash Register - Wiring, 884, 1974 (Box 109, Folder 2)
- Boore, David M., 1973-1979 (Box 73, Folder 26)
- Botanical Garden, 1925-1934 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Bothwell, Robert L. (PACE Office - Port.), 1963 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Bowling Alley - Campus, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Bowman Alumni House - Construction - addition to, 1954-1956 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Bowman Alumni Remodeling - Legal, 1965 (Box 102, Folder 27)
- Boyce, Richard D., 1959-1965 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Boys Town Interim Space, (901), 1974-1975 (Box 108, Folder 27)
- Bradbury, Norris E. & Lois Platt, 1936-1950 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Branner - Toyon Quad - Master Site Plan, 1962-1964 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Brian, Lawrence G., 1956-1972 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Briggs, Winslow R., 1960-1968 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Brinton, James R., 1961-1965 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Buchanan Street Property, 1926-1927 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Budget Developmt., 1977 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Budget, 1977-1978 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Budgets (General), 1967-1968 (Box 73, Folder 20)
- Building 1 - 250 Minor Renov. - Classics, 710, 1972-1973 (Box 104, Folder 6)
- Building 1 - Alterations, 713, 1972-1973 (Box 105, Folder 9)
- Building 1 - Basement Renovation, 839, 1973-1975 (Box 103, Folder 26)
- Building 1 - Rooms 1L & 1H Alterations, 724, 1972-1973 (Box 105, Folder 11)
- Building 1-10, Room 11G - President’s Office Alterations, 843, 1973-1975 (Box 103, Folder 27)
- Building 10 - Legal, 1968-1969 (reconstruction of President’s Office after fire, summer 1968) (Box 102, Folder 30)
- Building 110 Renovations - Legal, 1967-1968 (Box 103, Folder 11)
- Building 120 - Affirmative Action Program, 593A, 1972 (Box 115, Folder 12)
- Building 120 - Affirmative Action Reports, File I, 593A, 1972 (Box 115, Folder 14)
- Building 120 - Affirmative Action Reports, File II, 593A, 1972 (Box 115, Folder 13)
- Building 120 - Bulletins, Supplements, 593A, 1972 (Box 115, Folder 6)
- Building 120 - Contract Changes, 593A, 1972 (Box 115, Folder 5)
- Building 120 - Exhibits, 593A (Box 115, Folder 11)
- Building 120 - Field Inspector’s Progress Report, 593A, 1972-1973 (Box 115, Folder 7)
- Building 120 - General Correspondence, 593A, 1971-1974 (Box 115, Folder 9)
- Building 120 - Job Site Meetings, 1972-1973 (Box 115, Folder 10)
- Building 120 - Legal, 593A, 1972-1973 (Box 115, Folder 4)
- Building 120 -Budget & Fiscal, 1972-1974 (Box 115, Folder 8)
- Building 2-520, Room 524 - Hydraulics Laboratory Heating, 844, 1973-1975 (Box 109, Folder 7)
- Building 200 - Portuguese & Spanish), 593C, 1971-1973 (Box 104, Folder 4)
- Building 500 - Tire Noise Research Renovation, 835, 1973-1974 (Box 104, Folder 3)
- Building 500, Engineering- Emergency Light and Stair Rails, 823, 1973-1974 (Box 103, Folder 24)
- Building 540 Cairns - Budget Study, 665, 1971-1975 (Box 104, Folder 10)
- Building 540 Partial Renovation - Engfer Iron Works, 665, 1973 (Box 104, Folder 13)
- Building 540 Partial Renovation, File II - Welch Contract, 665, 1973-1975 (Box 104, Folder 11)
- Building 540 Partial Renovation, File III - Elevator Contract, 665, 1972-1974 (Box 104, Folder 12)
- Building 540 West Coast Rebar Listing, 665, 1973 (Box 104, Folder 9)
- Building 80, Rm. 84 & 85 Alterations, 820, 1973-1974 (Box 103, Folder 23)
- Building 80, Room 85, Alteration, 852, 1973-1974 (Box 103, Folder 30)
- Building Systems Development, 1974 (Binder) (Box 35)
- Bunker, John P. M.D., 1960-1965 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Bunker, John P., 1965-1968 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Business Affairs, Office of the V.P. for - Project Planning Minutes, 1969 (Box 94, Folder 1)
- Business Affairs, Office of the V.P. for - Project Planning Minutes, 1967 (Box 93, Folder 19)
- Business Affairs, Office of the V.P. for - Project Planning Minutes, 1968 (Box 93, Folder 15)
- Business Affairs, Office of the V.P. for - Project Planning Minutes, 1969 (Box 93, Folder 20)
- Business Affairs, Office of the V.P. for - Project Planning Minutes, 1970 (Box 93, Folder 21)
- Business Affairs, Office of the V.P. for - Staff Meeting Minutes, 1967 (Box 93, Folder 17)
- Business Affairs, Office of the V.P. for - Staff Meeting Minutes, 1968 (Box 93, Folder 16)
- Business Affairs, Office of the V.P. for #1, 1947-1965 (Box 93, Folder 18)
- Buy vs Lease Analysis (Bus), 1977 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- By-Laws, 1942-1944 (Box 94, Folder 2)
- California Avenue, 1641 - Rental Property, 1950-1962 (Box 94, Folder 5)
- California, Dept. Agriculture - Bureau of Nursery Service, 1940-1947 (Box 94, Folder 3)
- California, State Board of Equalization, 1947-1956 (Box 94, Folder 7)
- California, State of - Department of Education, 1958-1967 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- California, State of - Department of Fish & Game at Hopkins Mar., 1948-1970 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- California, State of - Department of Fish and Game, 1954-1961 (Box 94, Folder 6)
- California, State of - Department of Industrial Relations, 1940-1961 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- California, State of - Department of Public Health - Bubonic Plague, 1943-1944 (Box 94, Folder 4)
- California, State of - Dept. Agriculture Division of - Animal Husbandry, 1937-1954 (Box 94, Folder 10)
- California, State of - Div. of Fish and Game Grants and Agreements, 1935-1947 (Box 94, Folder 9)
- California, State of - General, 1950-1971 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- California, State of - Sales and Use Tax re Stanford Union, 1933-1941 (Box 94, Folder 11)
- California, State of - Sales and Use Tax, 1941-1952 (Box 94, Folder 8)
- Campus - Subdivision Development - Rejected, 1949-1950 (Box 94, Folder 12)
- Campus Guest House (Conference Center), proposed, 1965 (Box 94, Folder 13)
- Campus Housing - Planning Information, 1969-1971 (Box 73, Folder 21)
- Campus Property - Interdale Apartments, 1946-1951 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Campus Residences for Possible Academic Use, 1956-1967 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Cancer Virus Trailer Renovation, 655, 1973-1975 (Box 109, Folder 28)
- Carnegie Institution of Washington #1, 1933-1968 (Box 94, Folder 14)
- Carriages (Stanford, Donohue & Lathrop), 1941-1971 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Carter, Frank E. and Ida Elizabeth, 1945-1963 (Box 94, Folder 15)
- Cash Flow for M. A., 1977 (Box 33, Folder 12)
- Central Cooling Building - Legal, 1967-1969 (Box 103, Folder 10)
- Central Food Service Building - Legal, 1968-1970 (Box 102, Folder 6)
- Central Food Service Building, 1966-1971 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Centrex Building - Affirmative Action Report, #546, 1973 (Box 111, Folder 23)
- Centrex Building - Budget & Fiscal, #546, 1972-1974 (Box 111, Folder 18)
- Centrex Building - Bulletins, Supplements, #546, 1973 (Box 111, Folder 21)
- Centrex Building - Contract Changes, #546, 1973-1974 (Box 111, Folder 20)
- Centrex Building - Disbursements, #546, 1973-1974 (Box 111, Folder 17)
- Centrex Building - Exhibits, #546 (empty) (Box 111, Folder 25)
- Centrex Building - Field Inspector’s Progress Report, #546, 1973-1974 (Box 111, Folder 26)
- Centrex Building - Foundation Investigation, #546, 1972 (Box 111, Folder 27)
- Centrex Building - General Correspondence, #546, 1972-1975 (Box 111, Folder 19)
- Centrex Building - Job Site Meetings, 1973 (Box 111, Folder 29)
- Centrex Building - Legal, #546, 1972-1974 (Box 111, Folder 16)
- Centrex Building - Soil Report, #546, 1973 (Box 111, Folder 28)
- Centrex Building - Telephone Facility - Affirmative Action Program, #546, 1973 (Box 111, Folder 22)
- Centrex Building - Testing Laboratory Reports, #546, 1973 (Box 111, Folder 24)
- Centrex Ducts - Affirmative Action Reports, #546A, 1973 (Box 111, Folder 31)
- Centrex Ducts - Construction, #546A, 1973-1974 (Box 111, Folder 32)
- Centrex Ducts, File 1, #546A, 1973-1974 (Box 111, Folder 30)
- Chamber of Commerce - Correspondence, 1947-1960 (Box 94, Folder 16)
- Chamber of Commerce and Junior Chamber of Commerce, 1960-1973 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Chancellor of the University, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Chargeouts, 1974-1977 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Chemical Engineering Building - Legal, 179, 1964-1967 (Box 103, Folder 9)
- Chemistry Bldg., 1974 (Box 33, Folder 47)
- Chenery, Hollis B. (Mrs.), 1952-1965 (Box 94, Folder 17)
- Chi Psi Lodge, 1939-1960 (Box 94, Folder 19)
- Child Day Care Center, 1969-1970 (Box 94, Folder 18)
- Children's Hospital - Speech & Language Bldg. Upgrading, (907), 1974-1975 (Box 108, Folder 25)
- Chinese Students Club, 1934-1973 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Christmas Tree Lots #1, 1957-1973 (Box 94, Folder 20)
- Chron 1977 December (Box 99, Folder 13)
- Chron 1977 March - August (Box 99, Folder 17)
- Chron 1977 November (Box 99, Folder 14)
- Chron 1977 October (Box 99, Folder 15)
- Chron 1977 September (Box 99, Folder 16)
- Chron 1978 April (Box 99, Folder 9)
- Chron 1978 August (Box 99, Folder 5)
- Chron 1978 December (Box 99, Folder 1)
- Chron 1978 February (Box 99, Folder 11)
- Chron 1978 January (Box 99, Folder 12)
- Chron 1978 July (Box 99, Folder 6)
- Chron 1978 June (Box 99, Folder 7)
- Chron 1978 March (Box 99, Folder 10)
- Chron 1978 May (Box 99, Folder 8)
- Chron 1978 November (Box 99, Folder 2)
- Chron 1978 October (Box 99, Folder 3)
- Chron 1978 September (Box 99, Folder 4)
- Civil Rights - Equal Employment Opportunity - Stanford Correspondence & Reports, 1967-1969 (Box 18, Folder 12)